声明: 本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
欢迎访问官方论坛  www.YYeTs.net 在线观看 剧情讨论 学习交流
=====本字幕由以下成员荣誉制作 感谢他们的无私奉献======
翻译：Requiem校对：扣扣
后期：阿胜 双语制作：tamama788
========== 字幕总监制：七色九天 ==========
前情提要
Previously on Lost
有人看见Ethan了吗?
Has anyone seen Ethan?
恩  恩  他去海滩了
Yeah  Yeah  He took off on the path to the beach
看起来这里发生过一场争斗
Looks like there might have been a struggle
我想他们是被带走了
I think they've been taken
如果你再跟着我
If you do not stop following me
我会把他们的其中一个杀掉
I will kill one of them.
这边!
Over here!
Jack!
Jack在哪儿?
Hey. Where's Jack?
-我们需要医生!  -他在那儿!
-We need a doctor!  -He's right there.
-就在那儿  -快找人来!
-Right there.  -Find someone!
发生什么事了?
What happened?
-Jack!  -医生!
-Jack!  -Doctor!
Claire! 她还活着?
Claire! Is she alive?
-发生什么事了?  -她还好吗?
-What happened?  -Is she all right?
她没事吧?
Is she okay?
你在哪找到她的?
Where'd you find her?
往北一英里 当时我们正在找狗
A mile north.We were looking for the dog.
-那时她还有意识吗?  -她昏倒在我的手臂上
-Was she Conscious?  -She collapsed in my arms.
-她说什么了吗?  -天啊 她有没受伤?
-Did she say anything?  -Holy man! Is she injured?
她没事吧?
Is she all right?
大家退后一点 好吗?
Everybody needs to back off, okay?
让她呼吸点新鲜空气
Just give her some air.
Claire 能听到我说话吗?
Claire. Can you hear me?
醒醒  Claire
Wake up now. Hey. Claire.
Claire
醒醒
Wake up now.
没事了
It's okay.
Claire
没事了
Hey, it's okay.
It's okay.
Claire
没事了
Okay.
你已经安全了
You're safe.
你是谁?
Who are you?
你们是谁?!
Who are you?!
你们这些人是谁?!
Who are you people?
我不明白
I don't understand.
我不认识什么Ethan
I don't know any Ethan.
我不...我不记得了
I... I don't remember.
我不记得你们中的任何一个
I don't remember any of you.
我也不记得这一切
I don't remember any of this.
那你记得什么?
What do you remember?
我..我在一架飞机上
Um...I was on a plane...
从悉尼飞往洛杉矶
...um, flying to LA from Sydney.
Claire...
大家都在那架飞机上
We were all on that plane.
然后坠机了 掉在这个岛上
It crashed here, on this island.
这差不多是一个月前的事了
That was almost a month ago.
-不 我就要...  -你孩子没事儿
-No! I'm due...  -Your baby's fine.
他还会踢 一切都很正常
He's kicking. Everything's normal.
好吗?
Okay?
如果已经有一个月了 那为什么还没人来救我们?
Well, if it's been a month, then why hasn't somebody come to get us?
你知道发生什么事了?
我不知道
她还好吧
那女孩?
是的 我想应该没事
孩子呢?
我相信孩子也没事儿
你认为她是逃出来的吗?
You think she escaped?
你一直在我旁边 Boone你知道多少 我也就知道多少
You were right beside me, Boone. You know as much as I do.
她从哪儿来的?
But where'd she come from?
我意思是 我们都已经去过丛林深处了
I mean, we were out pretty deep.
那边根本没东西
Nothing's out there.
她没提到Ethan?
She didn't say anything about Ethan?
很明显 她根本不记得Ethan了
She doesn't even remember Ethan.
那家伙假装是我们中的一员
The guy pretends to be one of us
他把她拖进丛林里面差不多两个星期了
he drags her into the jungle for almost two weeks.
她会不记得他?
She doesn't remember him?
显然不记得
Apparently.
你觉得他在周围?
You think he's around?
我当然希望不了
I sure hope not.
Claire
这是你的日记
Here's your journal.
或许会有些帮助
It might help.
还有这是你睡觉的地方
And this is where you sleep.
很舒适 是吧?
It's quite cozy, isn't it?
当他..Ethan..
When he, Ethan...
当他把你带走的时候...
...when he took you away
也把我带走了
he took me too.
大伙都来追我们
The others came after us.
他们把我救回来了 但你...
They got me back. But you...
你却不见了
You were gone.
他..Ethan..是谁?
Who is he? Ethan?
Ethan...
Ethan是个坏人
Ethan's the bad guy.
所以那时.... 我们是在一起的
So we were together when...
是的
Yeah.
他为什么要放了你?
Well, why did he leave you?
这事我们明天早上再谈吧?!
Why don't we leave that lovely story for the morning?
你今天经历了够多了
You've had enough for one day.
-我睡不着  -哦
-I won't be sleeping.  -Oh...
我真是幸运
lucky for me.
我也不是个爱睡觉的家伙
Not much of a sleeper myself.
终于有个人陪我过夜了
Finally, I'll have someone to stay up with.
我们是朋友?
We're... We're friends?
是的
Yeah.
是的 我们是朋友
Yeah, we're friends.
感觉怎么样 老兄?
How's that feel, mate?
感觉他妈的秒极了
Sodding fantastic.
很好 因为 呃 我们快吸完了
Good, 'cause,uh,we're almost out.
但是我们还没吸完
But we're not out yet.
该享受的时候就享受 我的朋友
Carpe diem, my friend.
听着 把你的法语留给 那些懂得欣赏的人听吧
Look, save your French for someone who appreciates it.
是拉丁语 Tommy
Latin, Tommy.
是拉丁语
It's Latin.
那么 这句是拉丁文吗..
Well, is it Latin for...
"我有一大堆的钱  这样我们就能搞到很多非法药物"?
"I've got a pile of money so we can score vast quantities of illicit substances"?
不
No
如果你还不想戒毒的话
I suppose you ought to clean up then.
那么是时候该让你工作了
It's time to put you to work.
Lucy Heatherton小姐
Ms. Lucy Heatherton
22岁 各方面都很...成熟
22 and ripe in oh, so many wonderful ways.
刚从牛津大学毕业
Just graduated from Oxford,
和他老爸Francis Price Heatherton先生 一起住在骑士桥
and lives in Knightsbridge with dear old dad, Mr. Francis Price Heatherton,
他老爸绝对是个有钱人 朋友
who, my friend, is bloody loaded.
你哪里弄来这种老让我吃惊的消息 Tommy
How you amass this information never ceases to amaze me. Tommy
准备恋爱吧 来自传说中的驱轴摇滚乐团的Charlie先生?
Ready to fall in love, Mr. Charlie Pace of the legendary rock band Drive Shaft?
当然
Absolutely.
说真的 女士们
Oh! Seriously, ladies
不要再给我买酒喝了
I demand you stop buying me more drinks.
我是一个有道德的男人
I'm a man of high moral standing.
你那招勾引我回家的方法不管用的
Your obvious plan to take me home and ravish me will not work.
你们这群狐狸精
Saucy sirens.
我信奉一夫一妻制
I believe in monogamy.
我可不会像咖喱一样被人共享
I will not be shared like a common curry.
-我们的用意真有那么明显么?  -太明显了
-Are we that obvious?  -Dreadfully.
你们称自己为淑女? 简 奥斯丁定会感到羞耻
Call yourself ladies. Jane Austen would be ashamed.
那女孩怀孕了...就快生了
The girl is pregnant.Very pregnant.
那拿到我们应该相信她从他手里逃出来了?
Are we supposed to believe that she escaped from him?
-你什么意思?  -Ethan混入到我们当中
-What're you getting at?  -Ethan infiltrated us.
不管他是谁 来自什么地方
Whoever he is and wherever he comes from
他很聪明
he's intelligent.
谁能肯定Claire不是他派来的?
Who's to say he didn't even send Claire?
-你脑子有毛病啊 老兄  -Charlie 冷静
-You're off your head, mate.  -Charlie. Calm down.
这有点过分了 Sayid
That's a stretch, Sayid.
你倒是告诉我 医生 你以前诊断的有几个是真正的失忆症
Tell me, doctor, how many times have you diagnosed actual amnesia?
有几个是这种选择性失忆?!
And such a selective brand of it?
是 是很少 但她经历过严重的创伤
Okay. It's rare. But she's been through a major trauma.
记忆回到坠机前是有可能的
It is possible that her memory reset to the crash.
恢复记忆的机会有多少?
And the chances of that memory returning?
我不知道
I don't know.
知道吗? 随你们怎么谈论Claire吧
You know what? You boys talk about Claire all you want.
我要过去陪陪她
I'm actually gonna spend time with her.
我感觉她还有些烦躁
I get the impression she might still be a tad upset.
Jin!
你回山洞去?
You heading back to the caves?
你好
一块儿走更安全 对吧?
Safety in numbers, right?
当然...
Of course...
你根本不知道我在说什么
you have no idea what I'm talking about.
没有被卷入周围
How nice it must be to not be involved
一轮一轮的疯狂事多么好啊
in the bloody insanity that surrounds us at every turn.
这样真得很棒
It's quite beautiful really.
你只要照顾你的妻子
You take care of your wife.
其他的都是别人的事了
Everything else is someone else's problem.
不必参与任何决策
No need to be involved in the decision-making process.
不必对付能捍动大树的巨兽
No tree-shaking behemoths
不必研究法国人的求救信号
French transmissions
无知即是快乐
Just sweet bloody ignorance.
你知不知道你有多么的幸运?
You don't know how lucky you are,you know?
感觉一定很好 早上醒来 然后...
Must be nice. You wake up and...
怎么了?
What?
Charlie 我要她回来
Charlie, I want her back.
什么?我...
What? I...
我要你把她带回来
I want you to bring her back.
你对她做了什么?
What did you do to her?
你做过什么?!
What did you do?
你把她带到这儿
You bring her here.
如果你不乖乖照办的话
If you don't
我就杀了他们中的一个
I'm going to kill one of them.
明天日落前你还没把她带来的话
and then if you don't bring her back before sundown tomorrow
我就再杀一个...
I'll kill another...
再一个...
And another.
再一个
一天一个
One every day.
然后, Charlie...
And, Charlie...
我会最后一个杀你
I'll kill you last.
我们该怎么办?
What do we do?
我们去把他宰了
We go out and we bloody kill him.
冷静 Charlie 我们不想让其它人感到不安
Calm down. Charlie. We don't want the others to get upset.
管他们的 他现在就在那儿 Locke
Forget them. He's out there right now. Locke
我觉得他说的没错
I think he's right.
那家伙威胁要杀掉我们中的一个 除非我们把Claire带过去
The man threatens to kill one of us unless we bring him Claire.
那怎么办 难道我们就等着那一刻的到来吗?
and what? We just wait for that to happen?
我们以前跟踪过他 就一定能再跟踪一次
We tracked him once before. We can track him again.
你俩好像都忘了上次跟踪他的下场了吧
You both seem to have forgotten how that turned out.
他把你揍得半死
He bested you. Physically.
还把你吊在树上
He hung you from a tree.
徒手冲进丛林是搞不定他的
Running into the jungle unarmed is not gonna get the job done.
那怎么才能搞定他?
So, what does get it done?
我们封锁营地 把这件事有选择性的告诉小部分人
We circle the wagons, tell a select few about the threat
让他们分别在这儿和山洞那边放哨
we post them as sentries here and at the caves.
有选择性的告诉小部分人?
"Tell a select few"?
他说得出做得到 如果出了事 责任完全在我们
He does what he says he's gonna do, and that blood's on our hands.
好 Jack 那就告诉每个人
Okay, Jack, we tell everyone.
但你要是想保护他们  你就得考虑如何加强防御
But you wanna protect them, you need to start thinking defense.
大伙都撤离海滩 搬到山洞去
We move everybody off the beach back up into the caves.
要是Ethan不只一个人怎么办?
What if Ethan isn't alone?
也许他故意这样威胁我们...
What if he delivered his threat so that
让大家成为入瓮之鳖
we would gather like sheep to the slaughter
乖乖地聚在一起, 他们就能把我们一网打尽?
in a confined space where they could roll in and take us all in one fell swoop?
那好 John
Okay, John.
这么说来 你一定有好主意了 那么...
I mean, obviously you have a plan, so...
说来听听
let's hear it.
你知道发生什么事了吗?
发生什么事?
我怎么会知道?
或许其它人知道
其它人?
我被袭击都是因为他们干的好事
大伙都在避着我
The others are avoiding me.
-什么?  -没人愿意和我说话
-Sorry?  -No one will talk to me.
你知道 感觉就像发生了什么事
You know, it just feels like something's going on.
记起什么事了吗?
Anything coming back?
坠机后的事 都记不得了
After the crash, no.
反正这些事还是忘掉的好
Some of this stuff is probably better forgotten anyway
恩 我不知道你怎样
I don't know about you
但我们其他人都过得很开心
but the rest of us been having a wonderful time.
我们甚至建了个高尔夫球场
We even built a golf course.
你..你确定没发生什么事
You sure there's nothing going on?
当然
Absolutely.
好的
Okay.
你很自恋 是不是?
You're quite enamored of yourself,aren't you?
听着 Lucy 我知道这是我们的第一次约会 你应该表现得淑女一些
Now, Lucy, I know it's our first date, and you need to appear demure
但你知道 要是你想邀我和你上床 不必说"喝茶"
but if you want to invite me for sex,don't say "tea,"
说"做爱"
say "sex."
你到底喝不喝茶?
Do you want tea or not?
-来一杯  -很好
-I'd love some.  -Brilliant.
你老爸在哪儿?
So where is the old man?
我不知道
I don't know.
我想他是去斯劳镇收购某家造纸厂去了
I think he's buying some paper company up in Slough.
是这样 你俩相处的还算融洽吧?
Oh, yeah? You two get on?
事实上 我爸是个很酷的人
Dad's quite cool, actually.
当我告诉他我在和一个如假包换的摇滚明星约会时
He was rather proud when...
他还觉得很自豪
I told him I was going on a date with a bona fide rock star.
那是温斯顿 邱吉尔的东西
It was Winston Churchill's.
爸爸老收集大英帝国将领的各种垃圾东西
Dad collects all sorts of rubbish from the great leaders of the empire.
你应该见见他了
Hey, you should meet him.
温斯顿? 不 谢谢 我听说他都发霉了
Winston? No, thanks. I heard he's quite moldy.
我爸爸
My father.
他明天回来
He's coming back tomorrow.
你应该来吃晚饭
You should come around for dinner.
我非常乐意
I'd love to.
好极了
Excellent.
你看来饿了
You look hungry.
谢谢
Thanks.
Locke告诉我们出什么事了
Locke told us what happened.
你觉得他要回她干什么?
Why do you think he wants her back?
我不知道
I don't know.
也许该是用你脖子上那把钥匙的时候了
Maybe it's time you used that key you've been wearing around your neck.
那长官的箱子里面有4把9毫米的枪
There are four 9-millimeters in the marshal's case...
哦-哦 不
Uh-uh. No.
我把枪分给大家
I hand them out
一有风吹草动 人们就会受到惊吓
someone hears something out n the jungle, gets scared...
射中自己人的机率
Chance of shooting each other
要比击中他的概率高多了
is higher than shooting him.
我们这里锋利的刀子已经不多了 Jack
We're beyond sharpening knives. Jack
我不会把枪分给那些未经过训练的人
I'm not putting guns in untrained hands.
试试看!
Trip it.
还不错
Not bad.
周围放四个就可以搞定了
Four of these around the perimeter will do the job.
我每隔20米就生一堆火
I have fires prepared at 20-meter intervals.
干得好
Excellent.
有些人自愿为大伙站岗
Some of the men have volunteered for sentry duty
我让他们轮流换班
I'm going to put them on rotating shifts.
算我一个
I'll take a shift.
好的
Okay.
当然好 就靠你了 Boone
Absolutely. We're counting on you. Boone
或许我们应该把她转移走
Maybe we should move her.
在这儿比较安全
She's safer here.
那座山怎么样?
What about the mountain?
-可能还有其它的山洞  -她在这儿更安全 Charlie
-There could be another cave.  -She's safer here. Charlie
-没人是安全的!  -嘿
-Nobody's safe!  -Hey.
Clare被他带走是我的错
It's my fault he took her
是我的责任 我应该照顾好她的 我应该...
I was responsible.I should've taken care of her.I should've...
Charlie 她不会有事的 好吗?
Charlie, nothing's gonna happen to her. Okay?
恩 好的
Yeah. Okay.
Charlie 我想我的宝贝女儿绝对同意
Well,Charlie I think my daughter would agree that
你是和我们一块儿共进晚餐的 给人印象最深的一个
you are the most impressive person who's ever had dinner with us.
您太过讲了 先生
My condolences, sir.
我不知道Lucy有没跟你提过
I don't know if Lucy mentioned it to you
我曾经也参加过乐队
but I was in a band once, you know.
乐队名叫"新教革命"
They were called The "Protestant Reformation".
是的..噢 很糟 是吧?
Yes. Ouch! Dreadful,huh?
你后来放弃了?
You gave it up, then?
那时我结婚了 Lucy也即将出生
Well, I was married, Lucy was on the way.
他妈妈--上帝保佑她--要我再试试
Her mum, god rest her soul, wanted me to keep trying,
但我想更实际一些
but I always wanted to be more practical.
或者说 更有责任感一些
Responsible, I guess.
你也知道 一个男人得养家 顾家
You know, a man has to provide,take care of his family.
得考虑到将来
A man has to think about the future.
当然还有一点 你的乐队糟糕透了
And, of course, your band was bloody awful.
是 那倒也是 不过那不重要
Yes, there was that too. Small detail.
那么 你们正在筹划新专集吗 Charlie?
So, are you working on a new album,Charlie?
我们现在关系不太融洽
We're in a bit of a hiatus right now.
Liam 我兄弟 刚生了个女儿 所以 你知道 我们...
Liam, my brother, just had a daughter.So, you know,..
先休息一阵儿
we're taking some time off.
事实上休息很长一段时间了
Quite a lot of time off actually
我们分开差不多有一年了
It's been a year since we were together.
我在考虑出单曲
I'm thinking of doing a solo project.
Liam和我其实联系并不多
Liam and I don't exactly keep in touch,
再加上我们之间还有些争执...
and there's been some problems with...
关于版税问题
royalties.
老实说 先生 呃...
The fact of the matter is, sir, uh,
我认为驱动轴乐队...已经玩完了
I think that Drive Shaft might be... dead.
你他妈接了个什么?
You took a sodding what?
-工作 Tommy  -做什么工作?
-A job.Tommy  -A job? Doing what?
推销复印机
Selling copiers.
你做推销复印机的工作
You took a job selling copiers?
我喜欢她
I like her.
-她是你的猎物啊  -不要那么说
-She's a moose.  -Don't say that.
你脑子发昏了 老兄?
Are you off your bleeding chump, man!
一个星期以来 我一直让你吸我的海洛因 作为投资
I've been getting you off on my scag for over a week now, on spec.
明白"投资"什么意思吗
Spec means "speculation."
是的 我知道"投资"什么意思
Yes, I know what "spec" means
现在 投资的意思是你要完成原定计划
In this case, the speculation that you'll execute your end of the plan
偷些有价值的东西 然后我去卖
and steal something of value which I can in turn sell.
等到那可怜家伙意识到东西丢了
By the time the poor hopeless bird realizes it's missing,
她也不会想到是你这位摇滚明星Charlie Pace
it never even occurs to her that rock star Charlie bloody Pace
干出这种偷鸡摸狗的事
could be responsible for such larceny
生活就还能继续了
and the bloody party continues.
听着 我...
Look, I...
我觉得Liam不会回来
I don't think Liam's coming back.
我得为我的将来考虑
I have to think about my future.
你的将来 说真的?
Your future? Really?
是的
Yes
你什么时候开始工作?
When do you start this job?
礼拜一
Monday.
恩 今天是礼拜五吧?
Well, today's Friday, isn't it?
整个周末没毒吸
A full weekend without a fix.
周一会很"好受"的
Monday should be bloody wonderful.
我倒要看看未来待你如何 Charlie?
Let's see how the future treats you then, eh, Charlie?
在这儿!
Over here.
在树这边!有东西触响警铃了!
through the tree line. Something tripped the alarm.
我想我们又找到一个失踪的漂流者了
I think we found another missing castaway.
-发生什么事了?  -他还有气吗?
-What happened?  -Is he alive?
哦 老天
Oh, God.
他怎么过的我们这关?
How did he get past us?
我以为他们已经把周围布置得天衣无缝了
I thought those guys had the full-on perimeter set up.
Locke说那不管用
Locke said it didn't matter.
他从水里上来的
He came in from the water.
你肯定那不是个意外?
You sure it wasn't an accident?
我是说 或许那家伙只是溺水了什么的
I mean, maybe the guy just drowned or something
他的脖子被折断了 连同他的双臂 所有手指骨...
His neck was broken, both his arms, all bones in his fingers...
哦 好了 我知道了
Yeah. Okay. Got it.
看来Steve抽中了那支短签
Guess old Steve drew the short straw.
老兄 他叫Scott
Dude, that was Scott.
Scott Jackson在圣克鲁斯为一家网络公司工作
Scott Jackson worked for an Internet company in Santa Cruz.
因业绩好获得了奖励...
He won a sales prize.
...免费的澳大利亚两周行
Two-week Australian vacation, all expenses paid.
他是个不错的家伙
He was a good guy.
抱歉我一直叫你Steve
I'm sorry I kept calling you Steve, man.
我想该说"阿门"了吧
Um... Amen, I guess.
我不知道该如何收尾
I don't know how to end these.
你好
Hi. Um...
为什么大家都盯着我看?
Why is everyone staring at me?
我没有盯着你看
I'm not staring at you.
你叫什么名字?
What's your name?
Shannon
Shannon  你在盯着我
Shannon, you're staring.
难道没人告诉过你?
You mean nobody's told you?
告诉我什么?
Told me what?
为什么?!
Why?
为什么你要骗我?!
Why did you lie to me?
恩 听着....
Okay, look...
是吗 你还有什么没告诉我?!
Yeah, What else didn't you tell me?
我只是觉得以你的记忆力没有什么你能做所的
I just thought with your memory there wasn't anything that you could do.
没有什么我能做的?!!
Nothing I could do?
你干吗老让我蒙在鼓里 Charlie?
Why would you keep me in the dark, Charlie?
我已经失去记忆了
I'm already in the dark.
对不起
Sorry.
我只是想照顾好你
I just wanted to take care of you.
我可以照顾我自己
I can take care of myself.
看看你自己 Charlie Pace一位人人敬仰的商业人士
Look at you. Charlie Pace, respectable businessman.
你没必要给我买这身西装的 Luce
You didn't have to buy me this suit,Luce
那你第一天上班打算穿什么?
And what did you intend on wearing for your first day of work?
我有衬衣...
I have shirts...
有纽扣的那种
with buttons.
你还好吧?
You okay?
是 我 我只是紧张而已
Yeah, it's...I'm just nervous.
不用紧张  爸爸都安排好了
Don't be. Dad's put the fix in.
他要求他们订购2台复印机 给你打气
He's demanded they buy two copiers to boost your confidence.
记住操作手册了吧?
Have you memorized the manual?
倒背如流
Backwards and forwards.
说来听听
Say something impressive.
Heatherton c815打印机的尖端扫描系统
The Heatherton C815 Copy Center's leading scan offerings
完美结合了文件读取
combine the benefits of document capture
和瞬时输出 随时 随地
with instant delivery anywhere, anytime.
-随时?  -随地 宝贝儿
-Anywhere?  -Anytime, baby.
在数以千计的狂热歌迷面前你都表演过了
You've been on stage in front of thousands of screaming fans.
这只不过是一些人 想买一些复印机罢了
This is just some men who want to buy a silly copy machine.
你会做得很好 我对你有信心
You're gonna do great. I believe in you.
差点忘了 在这儿等着
Oh! I almost forgot. Wait here.
好
Okay.
好 听着  我知道你又要抗议了
All right, I know you'll protest,
但要是没这样东西 别人就不会尊敬你
but you simply can't be respected unless you have one of these.
哦  Lucy
Oh, Lucy.
不用客气
You're welcome.
好 恩...
Okay, well...
我就要迟到了 那巴士...
I'm gonna be late. The bus...
巴士? 别傻了
The bus? Are you daft?
我开车送你去
I'm driving you.
哦 不 Lucy. 你不必这么做的
Oh, no,Lucy. I'd rather you didn't.
没有商量余地 东西都拿齐了?
No arguments. You have everything you need?
是的
Yeah.
那就去上班吧
Then let's get you to work.
John...
去走走?
Wanna take a walk?
今晚太阳下山前你觉得会发生什么事?
What do you think happens after the sun sets tonight?
恩 如果我们不把Claire带过去...
Well, if we don't bring Claire to him?
你这问题是白问 Jack
Rhetorical, Jack.
昨晚发生的事  今晚还是一样会发生
Same thing happens tonight happened last night.
你觉得你能否追踪到他?
You think you can track him?
什么?再说一遍?
What, I'm sorry?
我们知道他在哪儿袭击Jin和Charlie
We know where he attacked Jin and Charlie.
你觉得你能不能追踪到他?
Do you think you could pick up the trail?
恩 可能吧 但我不会这么做
Maybe, but I wouldn't.
你不会这么做?
You wouldn't?
Jack  我不是冷血动物
Jack, I'm not a cold man.
我同样为大家的损失感到痛心
I feel for the loss of one of our own.
但基本原则没有改变
But nothing fundamental's changed.
不管他是谁 从哪里来 我们都在Ethan的地盘上
Whoever he is, wherever he comes from, we're on Ethan's turf.
他占有优势
He has the advantage.
对他而言  我们只不过是一群...
To him we're nothing more than a bunch of
拿着尖木棍 吓破了胆的白痴
scared idiots with sharp sticks.
要是我说我有办法把优势夺回来呢?
What if I told you that I had a way to get the advantage back?
那我就要问那是什么方法了 Jack?
Then I would ask, "What way might that be?" Jack?
为什么 医生 你一直瞒着我们
Why, doctor, you've been holding out on us.
我想你应该知道怎么用这东西吧
I'm guessing you know how to handle one of these.
你们疯了?
Are you insane?
这是我们最好的机会了 Charlie
It's the best chance we have.Charlie
没门儿
No bloody way.
如果我们想要抓住Ethan 就得想办法把他引出来
If you want to capture Ethan, we have to ensnare him.
唯一的方法就是把他想要的东西给他
and the only way to do that is by giving him what he wants.
你根本不知道自己在讲什么
You have no idea what you talking about
这家伙...他会把你们都杀了的
This guy...he will kill all of you.
-你们无法保护自己  -Charlie
-You can't protect yourself...  -Charlie
不用你替我说话
I can talk for myself
Claire 他们要把你作诱饵
Claire They want to use you as bait.
我不记得Ethan
I don't remember Ethan.
我也不记得他对我做过什么
I don't remember what he did to me.
但要是我能够阻止他伤害其它人
But if I can help stop him from hurting anyone else,
我就必须真么做
I have to do that.
我和你们一块儿去 你说有四把枪
I'm coming with you. You said there were four guns.
你用过枪吗 Charlie?
You ever fire a weapon, Charlie?
好了 我们动手吧
All right, we should do this.
让我们想个策略
Let's figure out a game plan.
好的 Sayid 军人
All right, Sayid, soldier.
Locke  你当猎人
Locke, you're the hunter.
让我证明给你们看 C815运转的有多么神速 拿...
Allow me to demonstrate the awesome speed of the C815 using...
...你们的...
...one of your...
...技术手册来示范一下
...technical manuals.
没问题 可能是...
Not a problem. There's probably...
...这儿写着...
something in here.
没什么能...
Nothing to...
马上 马上
One second. One second.
稍等一下
Bear with me.
Charlie说的对
Charlie's right.
什么?
About what?
我们有四把枪 就得配四个人
We have four guns. We should have four men.
帮忙?
Help?
我?
Moi?
你到底知道不知道怎么用枪?
You know how to handle a gun or not?
哦 我想至少有只北极熊知道我会用
Well,I know at least one polar bear seems to think so.
这家伙你哪儿弄来的 老兄?
Where'd you get the hardware, hoss?
我也想去
I wanna come.
抱歉 没枪了
Sorry. We're out of guns.
没有枪就不能去那里
And no one goes out there unarmed.
你有多少弹药?
How much ammo you got?
差不多100发
Hundred rounds, give or take.
都是9毫米的 对吧?
All nines, right?
9毫米? 枪?
Nine millimeters? The guns?
是的 怎么了?
Yeah. Why?
如果这位女士想去...
'Cause if the lady wants to come...
这是我早些时候从长官那儿拿的
Lifted this off the marshal back in the old days.
你还记得他吧?
You remember him, don't you?
阴沉的家伙 下颚比较方的那个?
Surly guy, kind of a square jaw?
别着一把9毫米西格手枪?
Carried a Sig nine?
是的 我记得是你向他开的枪...
Yeah. I remember you shot him.
并且打偏了
And missed.
是的 好吧...
Yeah, well...
过去的事就不提了
bygones.
不管怎样...
And, hell...
五把枪总比四把枪好
five guns are better than four.
我们五个人分布在你周围
You'll be surrounded at five points.
每个人都会在你的视线之内
Everyone will be in visual contact with you.
一定要待在我告诉你的那地方
Make sure you stay in the area I've shown you.
还要记住 不到最后时刻不要开枪
And remember, the guns are a measure of the last resort.
我们要抓活的
We want him alive.
在这边!这边!
Over here.
Jack抓住他了!
Jack's got him.
管好你们的枪 不要射击
Hold your fire. Don't shoot!
我们要抓活的
We want him alive.
Claire!
你没事吧?
You all right?
是的
Yeah.
在这儿!
Over here.
-嘿! 不要开枪!  -放松
-Hey! Hold your fire!  -Easy!
致命一击 胜出 干得好 医生
Winner by a knockout. Nice one, doc.
现在有人告诉我这狗杂种是谁了吧
Now maybe somebody can tell me who or what this son of a bitch is.
呃 呃 丛林小子 想都别想
Uh-uh-uh, jungle boy, not even for one sec.
Charlie!
你为什么这么做 Charlie?
Why did you do it, Charlie?
因为他死有应得
'Cause he deserved to die.
他本可以告诉我们他从哪儿来的
He could've told us where he came from.
他要Claire做什么 为什么要把她带走
What he wanted with Claire, why he even took her
你真以为他会告诉我们 Jack?
Do you really think he would've told us anything Jack?
我不会再让那畜生接近她半步
I wasn't gonna let that animal anywhere near her again.
绝不
Ever.
Lucy
对不起 我一直问题缠身
I'm sorry. I've been having some problems.
请你听我解释一下...
If I could just explain...
走吧 Charlie
Leave, Charlie.
Lucy
我错了
I made a mistake.
你做错了?
You made a mistake?
我父亲的销售经理来我家
My father's sales manager comes to my house
来归还那香烟盒
to return a cigarette case
那个急诊大夫从你西装口袋里拿出来的香烟盒
that the EMTs pulled from your suit pocket at the bloody hospital
闻起来还有你恶心的味道
and it still smells of your sick.
-Lucy 我不是故意要...  -哦 你是故意的 Charlie
-I didn't mean...  -Oh, you meant to.Charlie
你从一开始就预谋好了
You meant to from the start.
你是个骗子
You're a liar.
我这么相信你 你却骗我
I believed you, and you lied!
我以为你想...
I thought you wanted to...
你说过...
You said...
你这自私的狗杂种!
You selfish bastard!
Lucy 能不能让我解释...
Lucy If I can just explain...
告诉我一件事就行了
Just tell me one thing,
而且你绝不许再骗我
and don't you dare lie to me.
我知道你为什么假装喜欢我了
I get why you pretended to like me.
我知道你为什么要偷...
I understand why you stole,
因为你是个瘾君子
because you're a junkie,
但我不明白你为什么要接那份工作
but I don't understand why you took the job.
你为什么要接那份工作 Charlie?
Why did you take the job, Charlie?
我想 我...
I guess I...
我...
I...
我想得到大家的尊重
...wanted to be respectable.
我想要你知道 我能照顾好你
I wanted you to think that I could take care of you.
你谁都照顾不好
You'll never take care of anyone.
我记起花生酱了
I remember peanut butter.
我怎么会记得花生酱?
Why do I remember peanut butter?
事实上 那是想象出来的花生酱
It was imaginary peanut butter, actually.
我不知道我怎么了
I don't know what happened to me.
我很害怕
I'm scared.
我愿意信任你
I want to trust you.
晚安  Charlie
Good night, Charlie.
晚安  Claire
Good night, Claire.
==============|  YYeTs字幕组招募启示  |==============
英文字幕录制(居住在加拿大和美国)  双语字幕校正   时间轴调整
英语翻译   欧美影视新闻翻译  影视评论  论坛版主  美工人员
服务器提供者  发布宣传  联系地址：www.YYeTs.com
==== YYeTs属于网络爱好者组织 加入者仅凭个人兴趣爱好 无报酬 ====